{
    "id": "226e05e533a04185a1ff6a840cbd8c53",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "You must abide …………………. the terms of this agreement.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "by",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This part of the country abounds ....................... rare metals.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "in",
                "on"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "He has been absent .....................… the class for two weeks now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "with",
                "to",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 3
        },
        {
            "question": "He was absorbed ....................... his work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "at",
                "in"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "You must abstain ...................... smoking and drinking.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "from",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "We cannot accede .....................… this request.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "This suggestion is not acceptable ………………….. me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Millions of people still do not have access ..................... . the internet.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "He was accused ………………….. theft.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "of",
                "against"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I am not acquainted ...................... him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        }
    ]
}